{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Name the missing partner in the famous duos.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Ken",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Barbie & ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Gretel",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Hansel & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "David",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "_____ & Goliath"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lady",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "____ & the Tramp"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hyde",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Jekyll & ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hutch",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Starsky & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ferb",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Phineas & ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mindy",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Mork & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chong",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Cheech & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ren",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "___ & Stimpy"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hall",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "____ & Oates"
  }, {
    "answer": "Clark",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Lewis & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Samson",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "______ & Delilah"
  }, {
    "answer": "Teller",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Penn & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Rocky",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "_____ & Bullwinkle"
  }, {
    "answer": "Costello",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Abbott & ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Roy",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Siegfried & ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sullivan",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Gilbert & ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Regis",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "_____ & Kathie Lee"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ebert",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Siskel & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Wayne",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "_____ & Garth"
  }, {
    "answer": "Gomez",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "_____ & Morticia"
  }, {
    "answer": "Guildenstern",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "Rosencrantz & ____________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jeeves",
    "category": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
    "question": "______ & Wooster"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Famous Duos Quiz #2",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/famous-duos-quiz-2.php"
}